《绝望主妇》前情提要
Previously on Desperate Housewives
任何事情都有起因
There is a motive to every mystery...
你身体的反应不是
Your body isn't responding to
这药应该有的效果
the medication the way it should.
我可能心脏病犯了
I think I'm having a heart attack.
任何罪恶都有证据
...Evidence of every crime...
他们因为仇视罪把你抓起来
They're charging you with a hate crime?
我以为你跟他偷情
I thought you were cheating with him.
跟我们的同志电视修理工
With our gay cable guy?
我不知道他是同性恋
I didn't know he was gay.
我也不知道贾斯丁是
I didn't know Justin was either.
任何问题都有答案
...And an answer to every question.
加布 这个女人自杀了
Gabby, the woman killed herself.
一定有什么事情发生
Something must have been going on.
你只需要靠近些 仔细看
All you have to do is take a closer look.
里面有个女人 她被分尸了
It had a woman in it. She was all chopped up.
最终 每个秘密
And eventually, every secret...
你知道保罗·杨在哪儿吗
Do you know where Paul Young is?
我知道他周四晚会去哪儿
I know where he'll be on Thursday night.
都将真相大白
...will be revealed.
玛丽·艾莉丝被勒索了
Mary Alice was being blackmailed?
玛丽·艾莉丝 你到底做了什么
0h, Mary Alice, what did you do?
我叫玛丽·艾莉丝·杨
My name is Mary Alice Young.
我在世的时候 我的生活充满了
Before I died, my life was filled
爱 欢笑 友情
with love, laughter, friendship,
不幸的是 还有秘密
And sadly, secrets.
这个秘密始于15年前
The secrets had begun 15 years earlier
那时我的名字叫安吉拉·福里斯特
when my name was Angela Forrest,
我生活平静 却暗潮涌动
and I was living a life of quiet desperation.
这样的感觉会出现在
I'd felt it every morning
每天早上给我丈夫做早餐的时候
as I made breakfast for my husband.
你能去下超市吗
Could you could stop by the market?
我的剃须膏用完了
I'm out of shaving cream.
出现在我下午出去办事的时候
And during the errands I ran in the afternoons...
你要是周五来的话就能省下很多了
You'll save a bunch if you come on Fridays.
甚至出现在我每晚上班的时候
...Even at my work every evening...
好漂亮的日历 照片是在附近拍的吗
What a lovely calendar. Was this taken around here?
不是 是美景镇 我家人住那儿
No, that's way out in Fairview. I have family there.
太田园了
Isn't it idyllic?
给你 安吉拉 归档吧
Here, Angela. You can file this.
对我而言 每天都是灰色的 毫无意义
...To me, each day was gray and meaningless.
然后突然有一晚
And then one night, suddenly...
安吉拉
Hey, Angela. ...
生活有了一丝色彩
There was color.
黛德丽 你在这儿干什么
Deidre? What are you doing here?
我需要钱
I need some money.
黛德丽 给你
Deidre. Here.
-你又吸毒了是不是 -没有
- You're using again, aren't you? - No.
我只是要给我孩子买点吃的
I've just got to get some food for my baby.
和别的东西
Some other stuff.
如果孩子饿了 我们去超市买些东西吧
If the baby's hungry, we can go to the market and I'll buy food.
我能自己给我孩子买吃的
I can shop for my own baby, ok?
安静点 我不能思考了
Quiet. I can't think.
看到这个手表了吗 很值钱
See this watch? It's worth a lot.
50块我卖给你
I'll give it to you for 50 bucks.
-她不会给你钱 -能闭嘴吗
- She's not giving you money. - Do you mind?
安吉拉 你是在戒毒所
Angela, you're the only one at Rehab
唯一把我当人看的人
who treated me like a person.
求你了 别拒绝我
Please. Please don't stop now.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我把孩子卖给你
I'll sell you my baby.
-什么 -我知道你不能生育
- What? - I know you can't have your own.
-你很绝望 -你该离开了
- It's been killing you. - It's time that you left.
我在为丹娜着想
I'm thinking about Dana.
你能给他一个好的家庭环境
You'll give him a good home.
好吗 那对他更好
Ok? He'll be better off.
嘘 安静点
Shh! Quiet!
亲爱的
Honey.
你家里有多少钱
How much money do you keep in the house?
她不是有个十个月大的孩子吗 在哪儿
She has a ten-month-old baby. Where is it?
我不知道 如果我们看到孩子的话
I don't know. If we'd seen a kid
绝不会把他扔在那个破房子里的
we wouldn't have left it in a crack house.
那孩子要有个三长两短 你就别干了
Anything happens to that child, I will have your badge.
让我好好干我的活好吗
Just let me do my job, huh?
我们会派人守在她身边
We'll post an officer at the Junkie's bedside,
我们会问问她孩子在哪里
We'll let her tell us where she left her kid.
我衷心希望你们在美景镇过得开心
I really do hope you folks will be happy here in Fairview.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们确实很开心
And we were.
挥手拜拜 扎克
Wave bye, zach.
挥手 拜拜
Wave bye-bye.
我们是全世界最开心的家庭
We were as happy as any family could be.
直到三年后的某一晚
until one night three years later...
敲门声响起时
When there was a knock at our door.
我再一次陷入绝望
And I was desperate once again.
《绝望的主妇》第一季 第二十三集 第一季完
Desperate Housewives S01E23
清晨5点的紫藤郡
It was 5:00 in the morning on Wisteria Lane
电话响起
when the phone calls started.
从第一声铃响之时
Each of them knew something was wrong
每个人都知道有事发生了
from that first ring.
喂
Hello?
这是郊外社区一条不成文的规矩
It's an unwritten rule of suburbia...
喂
Hello?
半夜别打给邻居
Don't call the neighbors in the middle of the night
除非是坏消息
unless the news is bad.
喂
Hello?
所以他们来了
And so they came,
带着没梳过的秀发
with their uncombed hair
未上妆的脸颊
And their unmade faces.
他们来的原因是
They came because
在这么多年之后
after all these years...
布里
Bree.
他们已不仅仅是邻居而已
...They were no longer just neighbors.
你们怎么会在这里
What are you... doing here?
我们听说雷克斯心脏病发作
We heard Rex had a heart attack.
他怎么样了
How is he?
情况很稳定
Um... He's stable.
不过他们必须要置入心脏起搏器
But they have to put in a pacemaker,
他们在准备做手术
so they're gonna need to operate.
-你们怎么知道的 -丹妮尔打电话过来
- How did you guys know? - Danielle called.
你怎么样
So how are you doing?
我们在吵架
We were having a fight when he...
他就心脏病发作了
got the heart attack and...
我很内疚 因为我应该
I'm feeling guilty 'cause I should
更及时的把他送过来
have gotten him here sooner and...
亲爱的 这里的医生医术高明
Honey, the doctors here are great.
他那么年轻 他很快会好起来的
He's so young. He's gonna bounce right back.
你没什么可担心的
You have nothing to worry about.
你们知道吗 你们能来
You know what? I am so happy
我很高兴 真的
that you guys came here. I really am.
但我正努力让自己坚强
But I am trying hard to be strong,
如果你们继续安慰我
so if you keep comforting me...
你就会崩溃
You're gonna lose it?
那我们不安慰你了
Then we won't comfort.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们来说点不那么紧张的事情吧
We'll just talk about non-crisis things.
我想到了 我在麦克的杂物里面
Oh, I know. I found Mrs. Huber's journal
找到了胡博太太的日记
in some of Mike's stuff.
她知道了玛丽·艾莉丝的秘密
I think she knew Mary Alice's secret
并且勒索她
and was blackmailing her.
是啊 这话题真不紧张
Yep, that'll do it.
扎克 到这儿来 求你了
Zachary, come back here, please.
你父亲说了要离开一阵
Your father told you he would be gone for a while.
他说你该让我来照顾你
And he said you should let me look after you.
我自己能行 我不是小孩子了
I will be fine by myself. I am not a child.
我知道你不是小孩子
I know you're not a child,
但我们应该谈谈
but I think we should discuss this.
我很好 真的
I'm fine. Really.
你能跟我在一起
Why should you fend for yourself
你为什么要自己照顾自己呢
when you can just come home with me?
让我来照顾你 我很乐意
Let me shoulder the burden. It would be my pleasure.
你有什么毛病 让我一个人待着
What kind of freak are you? Just leave me alone.
你不是我妈妈
You are not my mother.
我跟你说过了我很好
I told you that I am fine.
别再假装我妈妈了 滚回去
Stop acting like my mother and go home.
我希望有那么容易 扎克
I wish it were that easy, Zachary,
为了你
for your sake,
但不行
but it's not.
你父亲不会回来了
Your father's not coming back.
-他说他会回来 -他撒谎了
- He said that he was. - He lied.
我想告诉你这些的
I wanted to spare you this,
不过你父亲跟我谈过了
but your father and I discussed it
他觉得自己
And he decided
不应该回来
that he shouldn't come back.
把你的包拿上 我们回家
Get your bag and let's go home.
我会给你做点布丁
I'm gonna make you some pudding.
你对我爸爸做了什么
What did you do to my dad?
告诉我
Tell me!
爱普怀特太太
Mrs. Applewhite?
什么事
Yes?
你好 我是伊迪·布利特
Hi. I'm Eddie Britt.
帮你买下这所房子的经纪人
The realtor who helped you buy this house.
没错 你好
Oh! of course. Hi.
我一直期待能见到你
Hi. I've been so curious to meet you.
是吗 为什么
Really? Why?
我以前从来没有光靠打电话
It's just that I've never sold
就卖出一套房子
a house over the phone before.
你真有勇气 没看过房就敢买
You were awfullly brave buying a place site unseen.
不是
Not really.
从广告上能看出 这就是我们要找的房子
We could tell from the advertisement it was just what we were looking for.
这是我儿子马修
This is my son, Matthew.
很高兴认识你 太太
It's nice to meet you, ma'am.
请叫我伊迪
Please, call me Edie.
太太是用来称呼中年妇女的
Ma'am is for middle-aged women.
比如她
Like her.
任何时候你都可以叫她太太
You can call her ma'am any time you want.
房子一切都好吧
So are you two finding everything ok?
我还没给你们介绍清楚呢
Because we didn't do our realtor's walkthrough.
一切都挺好
Everything is fine.
亲爱的 你们钱都付了
Oh, honey. Escrow's closed.
现在我可以指给你们看这房子哪里会漏雨
Now I can show you where to put the buckets when the rain comes.
伊迪 房子没问题
Edie, the house is fine.
谢谢你来看我们
But how lovely of you to stop by.
好 这是我的名片
Ok. Here is my card.
有事就跟我联系
Call any time you want.
再见
Bye.
这儿的邻居都挺友好的
People are very friendly in this neighborhood.
是的 挺友好
Yes. Yes, they are.
麦克 甜心 希望你的工作顺利
Mike, hi, sweetie. I hope the job's going well.
那么 希望你别生气
Um... So... I hope you're not mad
不过我在你的卡车里发现了胡博太太的日记
but I found Mrs. Huber's journal in your truck
然后我忍不住读了
and well, I couldn't exactly not read it, so I did,
我知道了勒索的事
and I know all about the blackmail,
给我打电话 我们谈谈
so call me, we'll talk.
爱你 再见
Love you. Bye.
我还没收到回电 我有点担心了
I haven't heard back and I was getting a little concerned.
我们大家讨论了这事
The girls and I were talking
认为可能是保罗·杨杀了胡博太太
and we think maybe Paul Young killed Mrs. Huber
如果是真的
and if he did
很可能杀你以前女朋友的也是他
maybe he killed your old girlfriend too.
我们真的应该谈谈
So we should really talk about this,
打电话给我 爱你 再见
so call me. I love you. Bye.
我想有个手机的意义
I thought the whole point of having a cell phone
无非就是让人能及时找到你吧
was so someone could reach you when they needed to talk.
你都不跟我联系 我们还怎么发展啊
How can we move forward as a couple if you won't communicate with me?
麦克 我需要你马上回电 我是说真的
Mike, I need you to call me back. I mean it.
爱你 再见
Love you. Bye.
对于刚才的话很抱歉
I'm so sorry for that last phone call.
那是出于担心
Um... Let's just say it was the worry talking.
我只是非常想跟你谈谈
I just really need to talk to you...
稍等一下 我有电话来了
Can you hang on? I got another call.
-你好 -是我
- Hello. - Hey, it's me.
天哪 你去哪儿了
Oh, my god! where have you been?
这儿信号很糟 不过我总算收到你的留言了
The reception's lousy up here but I got your messages.
对不起啊 上一条留言
I'm really sorry for that last message.
-我只是 -有点紧张
- I was just uh... - Stressed out?
对 就是紧张
Yes, let's call it stressed out.
你怎么拿到玛莎·胡博的日记的
Uh... So how did you get Martha Huber's journal?
她姐姐蒂尔曼太太给我的
Oh, her sister, Mrs. Tillman, gave it to me.
她在帮我做调查
She was helping me with my search.
我觉得我们应该把它交给警方
I just really think we need to give it to the police.
是的
um... Yeah.
-当然 绝对应该 -真的吗
- Yeah, absolutely. - Really?
等我下了班
Sure. Yeah. As soon as I get through with this job,
我们就约那个科普兰警探见面
we'll make an appointment with that detective. Copeland.
好 好极了
Great. That's great.
好吧 我们 几小时后见面
All right. So I'll... see you in a few hours.
好的 不过赶紧
Ok. Hurry, though.
我有种感觉 保罗·杨与此有关
I just have a feeling Paul young is in the middle of all of this.
我们不要急着下判断
Well, let's not rush to judgment.
-你怎么来了 -来给你作证 卡洛斯
- What are you doing here? - I'm here to testify for you, Carlos.
把那些东西摘掉好吗 这样子我没法给他穿
Can you take those off? There's no way I'm dressing him.
加布 感谢上帝你居然肯来
Gabby, thank god you're doing this.
又打了个同性恋 情况很糟
Beating up a second gay guy looks bad.
是的 卡洛斯 对某些人来说
Yes, well, Carlos, in some circles,
打人总是不对的
beating people up at all is frowned upon.
那么你是怎么改变主意的
So why did you change your mind?
我将会是你孩子的妈妈
Well, I'm about to be the mother of your child,
这意味着责任会更多
which means a lot of responsibility
自己的时间会更少
and little time for myself.
如果我帮你摆脱官司
So if I'm gonna get you out of this mess,
你得报答我
you have to reciprocate.
好的
Ok.
半夜孩子哭起来的时候
When the baby cries in the middle of night,
你要毫无怨言地起来
you're going to get up, without saying one word.
你还要负责开车带孩子看医生
Doctor's appointments, you're driving.
我可不想在我的玛莎拉蒂跑车里装儿童座椅
I'm not putting a car seat in my maserati.
还有你也得负责奶瓶相关事宜
And you will also be on bottle duty.
洗奶瓶 消毒奶瓶 冲奶什么的
That means washing, sterilizing and filling.
这样我能活得有些人样
That way I'll have some semblance of a life
就不会那么恨你了
and maybe I won't hate you so much.
好吧 我们走
All right. There we go.
就这么说定了
So we're good?
-法庭上见 -加布
- See you in court. - Hey, gabby.
我们不打算母乳喂养吗
Aren't we breastfeeding?
亲爱的 如果你能喂的话 加油
Oh, honey, if you can swing that one, more power to you.
我能给自己买个批萨吗
Can I buy my own pizza?
能 宝贝 如果你能付钱
You can, honey, if you can pay for it.
19 19 19分 拿走
That is 19, 19, 19-zip. Bring it.
和佩妮在这待一会儿 好吗
Just stay here with Penny for a second, ok?
汤姆
Tom.
是 当着你的面 20分 出局
Yes! In your face. That is 20-zip. Game. Out.
汤姆 你在干什么
Tom. What are you doin'?
玩桌球 还能是什么
Playing air hockey, what does it look like?
凯文 到你了
Kevin, you're up.
现在是中午 你不是应该在上班吗
Well, it's the middle of the day. Shouldn't you be at work?
不 我辞职了
Mm, no. I quit.
-不是吧 -真的
- You did not. - Yes.
昨天 我跟彼得森说他自己搞吧
Yesterday. Told Peterson he could stick it.
你没使全力吧 凯文 用点心
Boom! You're not bringing it, Kevin. Bring it.
能跟我谈一会吗 我不明白
Could you talk to me for a second? I don't understand.
什么 你跟彼得森的老婆说
What? You asked Peterson's wife to
千万不要升我的职
make sure he wouldn't promote me.
于是他大大提拔了安娜贝尔 所以我辞职了
So he gives a huge promotion to Annabel so I quit.
你有什么不明白的
What don't you understand?
好
Ok.
好 我们能不能回家谈谈 求你了
Ok. Could we go home and talk about this, please?
不 不谈 来吧 小笨蛋
No, we can't. Serve it up, meat.
你打算在这儿玩一整天游戏吗
You're just gonna stay here and play games all day?
不 我打算吃点冰淇淋
No, I'm gonna get some ice cream
然后去湖边
and then I'm gonna go to the lake,
可能租条小船 想干什么就干什么
maybe rent a boat, do whatever I feel like.
-天哪 -你输了
- God! - Got you!
汤姆
Tom...
回家去 勒奈特
Go home, Lynette. Go home
别让我说出什么过头的话 回家
before I say something I regret. Go home.
好吧 你
All right. You.
你再得一分 就能拿回你的自行车了
You score this next point, you get your bike back.
你在想什么
What are you thinking about?
我只是
Oh. Uh... I was just um...
想着我需要开展春季大扫除了
thinking that I need to start spring-cleaning.
-你不是已经做完了吗 -没有
- You haven't done that yet? - No,
我需要彻底清理雨水槽
and I need to clean out our rain gutters
和冰箱底下
and beneath the refrigerator,
而且我都不知多久
and I can't tell you how long it's been
没有换架子的面板了 所以
since I replaced the shelf liners so...
最后你将会擦亮我们的婚礼的餐具
You'll finish off with our wedding silver.
你怎么知道的
How did you know that?
这么些年 你以为我没注意
All those years, you didn't think I was paying attention.
其实我注意到了
But I was.
你知道我为什么要把它留在最后吗
Do you know why I save it for last?
不知道
No.
因为它让我想起我的菲阿姨
Because it makes me think of my aunt Fern.
我们结婚那天 我告诉她我多么幸福
On the day we got married, I told her how happy I was.
她跟我说 即使在最艰难的日子
She told me that even during bad times
也要记得好日子终归会来到
to always remember that the best was yet to come.
所以我一边擦亮它
So as I polish it,
一边想着你和孩子们 我们的生活
I think about you and the kids and our life.
她说得真对
And how right she was.
-我要动手术了 -我知道
- They're gonna operate on me. - I know.
我得嘱咐些什么 万一
I wanna say some stuff. I mean, just in case...
雷克斯 你什么也不必说
Rex, you don't have to say anything.
我为自己做的一切道歉
I'm sorry for everything I did.
分居 出轨 还有特殊爱好
The moving out, the infidelity, the sex stuff.
一切都无关紧要了
It doesn't matter.
从现在起 我们互不相欠了好吗
From here on in, can we just say that we're even?
-好的 -谢谢
- Ok. - Thanks.
要我说
And for the record,
你一定会安然度过这次手术的
you are gonna come through this operation just fine.
你这么有把握吗
How can you be so sure?
因为我说过 佳境未至
Because I told you... the best is yet to come.
咱们周日见 别忘了喂邦戈
So I'll see you Sunday. Don't forget to feed Bongo.
多谢提醒 我这就去
Thanks. I'll go do that now.
宝贝 你先上车
Go on in the car, sweetie.
我跟你妈妈有话说
I have to talk to your mom real quick.
这么说你决定和有前科的水管工姘居了
So you're gonna go live in sin with the plumber slash ex-con?
姘居从你口中说出挺可笑的
It's funny you should mention sin.
我想你之前私通也没差多少吧
I think adultery still falls in that category.
我不放心这么一个家伙整天在朱莉周围
I don't like the idea of this guy being around Julie 24/7.
他是个好人
He's a good person.
爸爸 麦克很不错的
Mike's cool, dad.
他关心我们 我喜欢他在我们身边
He cares about us a lot and I like having him around.
所以别来搅和
So don't mess this up.
你都听到了
You heard the girl.
可他不过是个水管工
He's still a plumber.
你要乖乖的 邦戈
You be a good boy, Bongo.
要不你就得饿着肚子睡觉
Or you're gonna go to bed hungry.
梅尔小姐
Hi, Miss Mayer.
请你坐下好吗
Will you sit down, please?
-我想去喝点水 -你最好别去
- I'm just gonna go get some water. - I'd rather you didn't.
别应声
Don't answer it.
我知道你在里面 苏珊
I know you're in there, Susan.
我看见你了
I can see you.
你不想跟我说话也行
If you don't want to talk to me, fine.
至少藏藏好吧 真没礼貌
At least have the courtesy to hide.
开门吧 但不准让她进来
All right, but don't let her in.
伊迪 真没想到你会来
Edie, what a pleasant surprise.
行了 麦克在家吗
Right. Is Mike home?
不在 他去修水管了 什么事
Uh... No. He's on a big plumbing job. What's up?
-我能进来吗 -为什么
- Can I come in? - Why?
我在挨家挨户地通告
I'm warning all the neighbors.
费莉西娅·蒂尔曼被袭击了
Felicia Tillman was attacked.
-真的吗 -在杨家里
- She was? - At the Young house.
他们送她去医院了 我吓坏了
They just took her away in an ambulance. I'm totally freaked out.
我的伙计还没来工地
My guys haven't shown up at the job site yet.
只有我一个人
I'm over there all alone.
能不能让我进来坐会儿
So do you think maybe I can come in and hang out for a while?
指着我 什么啊
Stick it up my... What?!
你还是快走吧
Just get the hell out of here.
上帝 你真是个婊子
God, you are such a bitch.
为什么这么做
Why?
我让蒂尔曼夫人告诉我
I asked Mrs. Tillman to tell me
我爸到底怎么回事 她说了
the truth about my father. She did.
她说什么
What did she say?
德尔非诺把我爸带走了 要杀了他
Mr. Delfino took my dad away to kill him.
现在我要杀掉德尔非诺
Now I'm gonna kill Mr. Delfino.
法官大人
You honor,
整件事情都缘于我的孤独寂寞
this whole mess is just a result of my loneliness.
我的婚姻不那么顺心
My marriage is a bit strained.
在卡洛斯被判有罪后
After Carlos was convicted...
现在还没人被定罪 索利斯夫人
No one's been convicted yet, Mrs. Solis.
这只是一次陪审团听证会
This is just a grand jury hearing.
不 我说的是他另一项罪名
Oh, no, I'm talking about his other crime.
好吧
Oh. Right.
请继续
Go ahead.
是这样 他在被本宅软禁的过程中
Anyways, he was placed under house arrest
当然他向来比较善妒
and he being the jealous man that he is,
所以每次我出门他都很不安
got a little crazy every time I left the house.
他知道其他男人拿什么眼神看我
He knows how men look at me and...
其实 是我没能给他安全感
Well, I didn't exactly ease his mind.
我让他误以为我有外遇
I... falsely led him to believe I was having an affair.
卡洛斯被软禁前
Before Carlos' house arrest,
他总是忙于事业 很少陪着我
he was always working and he was never with me.
所以我以为
I thought that
如果让他以为我有外遇
maybe if he believed I was having an affair...
他就会意识到应该好好珍惜我
he would realize he loved me.
我知道这听起来很蠢 我承认
I know it sounds stupid. I do. I just...
这跟这桩案件有关系吗
Is there a point to this?
我是说
My point is that
卡洛斯是个易怒 善妒的原始人
Carlos is an angry, jealous Neanderthal.
但他绝不是个殴打同志的恶棍
But he's not a gay-basher.
好了 够了 原告律师过来
All right. I've heard enough. Counsel, approach.
老实说 我不认为这是起仇视罪
I gotta be honest. I don't think we have a hate crime here.
知道吗 你打错人了
Just so you know, you beat up the wrong guy.
你就不奇怪你明明只有一块草坪
Didn't you think it was strange that you had the only lawn
却需要一周修剪三次吗
that needed to be mowed three times a week?
你死定了
You are so dead.
-你死定了 -肃静
- You are so dead. - Order!
不 卡洛斯
No! Carlos!
他又要打人了
He's doing it again!
上帝啊 谁去拦住他
For god's sake, somebody stop him!
住手
Stop it!
-肃静肃静 -我要杀了你
- We will have order! - I'll kill you!
-我要杀了你 -肃静
- I am going to kill you! - Order!
都坐下 注意庭内肃静
Please be seated. We will have order.
下车
Get out.
我不是想狡辩
I'm not trying to justify anything
但是玛莎·胡博罪有应得
but Martha Huber ruined lives.
她毁了我的家庭
For fun. She destroyed my family.
-跟她无关 -那我就不懂了
- This isn't about her. - I don't understand.
快走
Walk.
还记得第一次给你体检时
Remember when we first tested you,
你体内的钾含量有些过高吗
your potassium level was a bit high?
是的 所以你让我别吃香蕉
Yes. You made me stop eating bananas.
可之后的检查发现 钾含量还在攀升
But as we've continued testing, it's kept climbing.
经过一系列综合检测
We've now run an entire battery of tests
你的肾功能毫无异常
and your kidney function is fine.
这些钾肯定是你摄入的
It has to be something you're ingesting.
让我看看
Let me see.
这些数据显然不正常
These numbers can't be right.
你的三餐是谁负责的
Who prepares your meals?
布里
Bree.
我知道你们的婚姻有些问题
I understand you've been having some marital problems.
-慢着 -还记得那次沙拉事件吗
- Wait a minute. - Was there an incident at a salad bar?
明知你会过敏她还是给你吃洋葱
She gave you onions when she knew you were allergic.
那次是意外
That was an accident.
可你的确在服用大量的钾
You're getting this potassium from somewhere.
-出去 -雷克斯
- Get out. - Rex...
我说真的
I mean it.
出去
Get out.
把表格留下
Leave the chart.
我想再看看
I want to read it.
你过得开心吗
So did you have a fun day?
事实上 我很开心
As a matter of fact, I did.
是长久以来我最开心的一天
I probably had the most fun that I have had in a long time.
我真的没想让你辞职的
You know, I didn't tell you to quit.
你确实没有
No. No, no, no.
可你让我
But you made damn sure
接下来的20年哪儿也去不了
that I'd go nowhere for the next 20 years.
我无言以对
I don't know what to say.
你怎么不请求我原谅呢
I hear "please forgive me" is popular.
是啊 我很抱歉 真的对不起
Yes, I am sorry. I am so, so sorry.
我无意伤害你
I didn't want to hurt you.
我只是想保护我们的家庭
But I was trying to protect our family.
如果你升迁了
If you got a promotion,
我们会很久都见不到你
we never would have seen you.
你得到处出差
You would have been travelling all...
勒奈特 你是对的
Lynette, you're right.
你没做错
You're right. You're right.
升迁会毁了咱们的
That promotion would have just killed us.
所以这是个好办法
So this is gonna all work out.
什么意思
What does that mean?
意思是我可以好好休假了
It means that I can use the break.
也对
Oh. Well, yeah.
我想你也该好好休息一阵了
I think it would be good for you to take some time off.
不是一阵 是一直
No, not some time. Full-time.
我要做全职爸爸
I'm gonna be a stay-at-home dad.
不如这样 由你来赚钱养家
What the heck? You earn the living for a while.
汤姆 这太荒唐了
Tom, that's... crazy.
为什么 有什么荒唐的
Why? Why is it crazy?
我们都知道你在广告界比我更强
You and I both know that you're better at the ad game.
而且你一直在说当妈妈有多么难
And you tell me all the time how hard it is to be a mom.
是的 是很难 但我很喜欢这样
Well, yes, it is hard. But I love it, too.
我都当了六年妈妈了
I've been doing it for six years
我没有抱怨过 一直都没有
And I haven't complained... The entire time.
好吧 有道理
Fair enough. Fair enough.
但事实上
But be honest.
你更怀念你的工作 不是吗
Secretly, you miss the ad game, don't you?
你怀念有压力
You miss the pressure and the
有紧迫感 权利在手的生活
deadlines and the power lunches.
或者是我错了
Or am I wrong?
也许你只想继续让家务活伴随以后的生活
Maybe you want to sort dirty socks the rest of your life.
在我们匆忙做决定前
We should talk about this seriously
应该认真讨论一下
before we make any rash decisions.
我已经做好决定了 你回去工作
I already made the decision. You're going back to work.
扎克 至少让我给你找点吃的吧
Can I at least get you something to eat, Zach?
苏打水就可以 谢谢
Maybe a soda. Thanks.
我得说 你这么做是不对的
I gotta say, I think you're making a mistake.
麦克不可能杀任何人
Mike couldn't kill anybody.
我是指 这可能是个误会
I mean, this could just be a misunderstanding.
这不是什么误会
This is not a misunderstanding.
我知道你很愤怒
I know you're upset,
但是你妈妈会让你这么做吗
but is this what you think your mother would want you doing?
-也许不会 -没错
- Probably not. - Exactly.
因为你很有家教
Because she raised you right.
你经历了这么多 失去了母亲
Look, you have been through a lot. You've lost your mom.
对于年幼的妹妹发生的事
You're still carrying the guilt of
还背负着罪责
what happened to your baby sister.
-我从来没有妹妹 -我知道丹娜的存在
- I never had a baby sister. - Honey, I know about Dana.
你怎么这么蠢 我就是丹娜
How stupid are you? I'm Dana.
我妈妈有毒瘾
My mother was some junkie.
他们就把我偷走并且换了个名字
They stole me and changed my name.
我的整个生活都
They have been lying to me
充满了谎言 所有人都骗我
my entire life. Everyone lies to me!
我妈妈 爸爸 蒂尔曼夫人甚至还有朱莉
My mother, my father, Mrs. Tillman, even Julie.
你明白这对我的伤害有多大吗
Do you understand how much that hurts?
听着 扎克
Look, Zach.
我知道你很愤怒 我们坐下来谈谈
I know you're upset. Let's just sit down and talk.
为什么 这样你就也可以骗我了吗
Why? So you can lie to me also?
不准说话
No more talking.
- 你好 -布里 我是克雷格医生
- Hello? - Bree, it's Dr. Craig.
我在医院 恐怕要有些坏消息得通知你
I'm at the hospital and I'm afraid I have some bad news.
雷克斯十分钟前过世了
Rex passed away ten minutes ago.
但他的手术不是要在明天吗
But his operation is not until tomorrow.
我知道 他没能挺过来
I know. He just didn't make it.
十分抱歉 我们尽力了
I'm so sorry. We did everything we could.
-布里 -我在 你们当然尽力了
- Bree? - Yes. Of course you did.
谢谢你打电话过来
Thank you very much for calling.
本来在我后院就能搞定的事
This is a long way to go to do what
你却非要长途跋涉到这里来
you could have done in my back yard.
你真是很从容啊 走了这么久
You're kind of taking your time. Walking a lot.
你清楚自己在做什么吗
You sure you know what you're doing?
你以前真的杀过人吗
You ever had to kill anyone for real before?
真的
Yeah.
但看你走累了
But since you're so tired of walking,
我们就在这儿解决问题
let's just do this here.
显然 我不期待你能大发慈悲
I don't expect any favors from you, obviously.
但请你至少让我知道
But could you at least do me the
你为什么要这么做
courtesy of telling me why we're here?
你认识黛德丽
You knew Deidre.
我知道你对她做过什么
And I know what you did to her.
她只是个伤了心的问题少女
She was just a sad girl with a lot of problems.
她曾做过很多糟糕 疯狂 自私的事
She did some terrible, crazy, selfish stuff.
但请你告诉我她到底做错了什么
But you tell me what she ever
值得因此去送命
could have done to deserve death
死在像你这种人手里
at the hands of somebody like you.
这太复杂了
It's complicated.
太复杂了
It's so... complicated.
就这样 我的丈夫开始分享我的秘密
And just like that, my husband began sharing my secrets.
吃点萝卜 扎克
You want some carrot, Zachary?
我用生命守护的秘密
Secrets I had died to protect.
给你
There you go.
我们得在游泳池竣工前
We have to get that fence up in the
给后院装上栅栏
back yard before the pool's finished.
-知道了 -我很认真
- I know. - I'm serious.
你知道孩子很容易溺水的
You know kids are drawn to water.
你好 安吉拉
Hello, Angela.
你太会隐藏踪迹了
You did a good job covering your tracks.
我花了我爸很多钱才找到你们
I had to spend a lot of my father's money hunting you down.
祝贺你找到我们
Congratulations. You found us.
我从未告诉过警察真相
You know, I never told the police what happened.
你没有吗
You didn't?
他们也许会把丹娜送到福利院
They would have put Dana in foster care.
或者更糟 把他给我父亲
Or worse, given him to my father.
所以我一直在保密
So I kept our little secret.
我们十分感谢你
Well, we appreciate that.
你们可以看出 我已经改过了
Anyway, I guess you can see I've gotten myself cleaned up.
你看上去不错
Yes, you look lovely.
安吉拉 我不是你以前认识的那个人了
I'm not the same person you knew back then, Angela.
我现在生活的很好
I'm in a good place now.
你不能带走他
You can't have him.
我以前没找警察 不一定现在不会去
I didn't go to the police before but I can do it now.
-扎克是我们的孩子 -他的名字叫丹娜
- Zach is our son. - His name is Dana.
要是你认为我会把孩子给
If you think I'm giving my baby
一个瘾君子 你真是疯了
to some junkie, you're crazy.
-他不是你的孩子 -冷静
- He's not your baby. - Just calm down.
你总是那么趾高气扬
You were always so high and mighty,
看不起我们这种可怜的堕落的人
looking down on us poor degenerates,
假装想要帮助我们
Pretending you wanted to help when all
其实是想让自己有优越感
you really wanted was to feel superior.
-你个自以为是的混蛋 -你还在吸毒
- You self-righteous bitch. - You're still using.
见鬼去吧 你要干什么
Go to hell. What are you doing?
-让我看看你的手臂 -我说过我戒了
- Let me see your arm. - I said I'm clean!
-冷静一点 -你要去哪儿
- Just take it easy. - Where do you think you're going?
我要去找我的孩子 并带他回家
I'm getting my son and taking him home.
-保罗 拦住她 -拜托 下来
- Paul, stop her. - Please. Come on.
-坐下 -把你的手拿开
- Sit down! - Get your hands off me!
我们把他养大 我们是他的父母
We raised him! we're his parents!
好了
Come on.
保罗
Paul!
别担心 我会给他一个美满的家
Don't worry. I'll give him a good home.
不
No!
玛丽·艾莉丝 你干了什么
Oh, Mary Alice. What did you do?
妈妈
Mommy?
没事的 扎克
It's ok, Zach.
妈妈要借一下你的玩具箱
Mommy needs to borrow your toy chest.
你继续睡觉 好吗
You go back to sleep, ok?
我们要怎么办
What are we gonna do?
你说过明天有人来
You said they were pouring the
给游泳池浇铸水泥
Concrete for the pool tomorrow?
-你是认真的吗 -他们就再也找不到她了
- You can't be serious. - They'll never find her.
-我们可以把她放到玩具箱里 -装不下的
- We can put her in this. - She won't fit.
我们就硬把她塞进去
Then we'll have to make her fit.
-你在干什么 -看看有没有疤痕
- What are you doing? - Checking for track marks.
黛德丽有个孩子
Deidre had a baby?
让我们赶紧结束吧
Let's get this over with.
回首看这个世界 是件奇怪的事情
It's an odd thing to look back on the world,
看那些被我甩在身后的人
to watch those I left behind,
都以各自的方式生活 勇敢 坚决
each, in her own way, so brave, so determined,
又那么不顾一切
and so very desperate.
不顾一切的想要出去冒险
Desperate to venture out,
但又害怕走了之后会错过什么
but afraid of what she'll miss when she goes.
不顾一切的追求自己想要的东西
Desperate to get everything she wants,
即使不确定自己想要什么
Even when she's not exactly sure of what that is.
不顾一切的想要生活重归美好
Desperate for life to be perfect again,
虽然她知道 生活从未美满过
although she realizes it never really was.
不顾一切的想要一个更好的未来
Desperate for a better future,
如果她能找到逃离往事的方法
if she can find a way to escape her past.
我不只关注 我为她们欢呼
I not only watch, I cheer them on,
这些令人惊叹的女人们
these amazing women.
我真的很希望 她们能实现自己的梦想
I hope so much they'll find what they're looking for.
但是我知道不是所有人都可以
But I know not all of them will.
很不幸
Sadly...
生活不是这样进行的
That's just not the way life works.
不是所有的人 都有幸福的结局
Not everyone gets a happy ending.